[
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c55",
        "correctAnswer": "Iron Maiden",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Deep Purple",
            "Feeder",
            "Squeeze"
        ],
        "question": "Which English heavy metal band released the song 'Hallowed Be Thy Name'?",
        "tags": [
            "rock_music",
            "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d9b",
        "correctAnswer": "The Beach Boys",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Swans",
            "Three 6 Mafia",
            "The Velvet Underground"
        ],
        "question": "Which band includes 'Dennis Wilson'?",
        "tags": [
            "music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f01",
        "correctAnswer": "Ã‰mile Zola",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Alphonse Daudet",
            "Anatole France",
            "Charles Dickens"
        ],
        "question": "Which author wrote 'Germinal'?",
        "tags": [
            "literature",
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "id": "6243331ecfaae40c129613c0",
        "correctAnswer": "A Sow",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A Worker",
            "A Doe",
            "A Leopardess"
        ],
        "question": "What would you call a female badger?",
        "tags": [
            "science"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Sport & Leisure",
        "id": "6242e84a8c2538f9601d2f9b",
        "correctAnswer": "The Robins",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Red Devils",
            "The Whites",
            "The Hatters"
        ],
        "question": "What is the nickname of the English football team Bristol City?",
        "tags": [
            "sport"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62373fd7cb85f7ce9e949cc1",
        "correctAnswer": "Cabo Verde",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Samoa",
            "Albania",
            "Monaco"
        ],
        "question": "Praia is the capital city of which country?",
        "tags": [
            "capital_cities",
            "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62373fa5cb85f7ce9e949cad",
        "correctAnswer": "Belize",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Chile",
            "Algeria",
            "Central African Republic"
        ],
        "question": "Belmopan is the capital city of which country?",
        "tags": [
            "geography"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f98a",
        "correctAnswer": "The Old Man and the Sea",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Remains of the Day",
            "Their Eyes Were Watching God",
            "The Color Purple"
        ],
        "question": "Which book contains the character 'Santiago'?",
        "tags": [
            "literature",
            "classic_novels",
            "fictitious_characters",
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Society & Culture",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950302",
        "correctAnswer": "Cabbage Patch Kids",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Stretch Armstrong",
            "Slinky",
            "Care Bear"
        ],
        "question": "Xavier Roberts was the name associated with which eighties toy?",
        "tags": [
            "1980's",
            "names",
            "society_and_culture"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "Society & Culture",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fccf",
        "correctAnswer": "Dravidian",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Austronesian",
            "Afroasiatic",
            "Sino-Tibetan"
        ],
        "question": "The language 'Malayalam' belongs to which language family?",
        "tags": [
            "language",
            "society_and_culture"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "regions": []
    }
]